ED
What are you doing today?
I'm free.
And what are you going to do today?
Operation Evasive Action.
Whoo!
Goo.
See you soon.
Happy Birthday to you. Happy Birthday to you. Happy Birthday dear Kaho-chan
Ah!
I touched you!
Yay!
I'll do my best to be a flowery 23 years old.
Thank you very much.
Dangerous to eat.
It says Kobayashi.
Good night.
A little more like this.
Um...
I'd like to introduce our
Adult members
and the children's
and the children's tastes
I hope it comes out well.
Spoiler alert!
Did you?
Aww...
I'll edit this for you.
I'll put it on TikTok.
Did you get it?
Where are we?
Hokkaido!
We are Ebichu!
Each song! Let's give it all
Ebichu!
Fight!
Strong.
But that's okay. We'll keep looking for them today.
We always do our best.
I'll do my best.
Don't worry, even if I oversleep, I'll keep going.
I really thought I had to stop.
I didn't.
You don't have to go so far for a second, just turn your body around.
How's that?.
So you want me to go like this?
Just there for a second.
Thank you very much.